I'm ready.
You sure?
Uh-huh.
Okay, let me just straighten
out your helmet there.
Thanks, Daddy.
No, no. One daddy,
two mommies.
All right...
it's all yours.
Okay. Okay.
There you go! There you go!
There you go!
Phoebe:
Ben's first
big kid's bike--
This is so exciting.
Oh, yeah.
I remember mine.
It was my sixth birthday,
my dad took me to the park
and I got on it and...
it bent.
Yeah.
I never had a bike of my own.
What?!
Well, we didn't have
a lot of money, you know.
But the girl across the street
had the best bike.
It was pink, and it had
rainbow-colored tassels
hanging off the handle grips,
and-and-and a bell
and this big, white
wicker basket
with those plastic daisies
stuck on... ooh!
Oh, that sounds like
my first bike.
My dad gave me
his old one.
Did the girl
ever let you ride it?
No.
But she gave me the box
that it came in.
It had a picture of the bike
on the front.
So I would sit on it
and my stepdad would drag me
around the backyard.
That is so unfair.
Not really.
I got to drag him around, too.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Making holiday candy
for the neighbors.
I'm sorry, who?
I'm going to hang this basket
on the door
and then when the neighbors
walk by, they can all
take a piece.
But we don't know the neighbors.
I do.
There's, uh... let's see,
Guy With a Mustache
Smokes-A-Lot Lady...
some kids I've seen...
and a red-haired guy who does
not like to be called "Rusty."
See? This is exactly why
I'm making this candy.
We can learn their names
and get to know our neighbors.
Wouldn't it be easier
if we just moved?
Good morning.
Ah, somebody's
in a good mood.
Well, why shouldn't I be?
I have great friends
I have a wonderful job--
Where you can make out
with your assistant.
Oh...
Come on,
it's not a big deal.
We stayed up all night
coming up with a plan
so that us dating
will not be a problem.
Oh, yeah?
What's the plan?
( exhales )
We...
we are not...
going to let it...
be a problem.
Wow, it took you
all night to come
up with that plan?
Oh, well
you know,
we did other stuff, too.
( snickering )
Did you two...
Oh, Monica, come on.
I don't sleep with guys
on the first date.
Matt Wire, Mark Lynn,
Ben Wyatt...
Anymore!
Okay.
Hi. Tag, um...
I have a conference call today.
Is that correct?
Yes, at 4:00.
Okay, thank you.
That'll be all.
Wait. Wait.
( restrained giggle )
Did you see that?
That mail guy
had no idea
there was something
going on between us.
I'm going to get back
to my desk.
Okay, hard worker.
I'll remember to put that
in your evaluation.
My what?
Well, you've been here
for two months now
and your boss is required
to hand in
a performance evaluation.
But, you know...
there is one thing
that I have yet to evaluate.
( laughs )
Are you serious?
No. I've just always
wanted to do that.
Can you help me clean this up?
The basket is
totally empty!
My God, the neighbors
ate all the candy!
Well, either that, or, uh...
Joey!
Did you eat
Yeah.
all the neighbor candy?
Uh, well, yeah,
that was the plan
but by the time
I got to it
there was only
a couple pieces left.
Yeah, they've been
coming by all day.
They love it.
They love my candy?
Oh, man! I got
to go make more!
Hey, Mon...
you might want to make
some more lasagna, too
because something
might have happened
to a huge chunk
of it.
Ross, the neighbors
ate all my candy.
Mine stole my newspaper.
It's like a crime wave.
Pheebs, you, uh...
you got a second?
Sure.
Yeah...
ever since you, uh... told me
that story about that bike
I couldn't stop
thinking about it.
I mean, everyone
should have a first
bike, you know?
So...
( gasping )
Oh, my God, Ross!
You like it?
I love it!
Yeah?
Oh!
Oh... And I love you.
Not that way.
But the bike got you
a lot closer.
Ah!
Well, take it
downstairs.
You know, give it
a... test drive.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
My first bike!
Thank you for the best
present I've ever gotten.
You're welcome.
( laughing )
Oh, and Chandler's
about to cry.
( trembling ):
Am not.
( knocking at door )
Monica:
Who is that?
Don't worry,
I'm brave.
I am brave.
I... I am brave.
( rhythmic knocking on door )
No, no, no, no, no.
( weakly ):
Can you tell me
who is there, please?
My name's Gary.
I live upstairs.
Well...
Hi.
Hi. Do you know
what time it is?
It's candy time.
My roommate says that they taste
like little drops of heaven.
Oh, please.
Did you hear that?
"Little drops of heaven."
( both laughing )
4:00 A.M.
So...
can I get some candy?
I am sorry,
but some of us
have to get up early
and go to work.
He does not know that
I am not "some of us."
Um, listen, I'm sorry
but I'll put some out
first thing in the morning.
Well, okay, I'll swing by later.
You live in this building?
Mm-hmm.
Mmm!
Seems like I would have
remembered you.
Mmm! Night, Gare.
So did you read
your evaluation yet?
No. It was marked
"confidential."
I just sent it down
to Human Resources.
Okay, please.
You're kidding, right?
I wrote that one
as a joke for you.
A joke they would appreciate?
I'm thinking "no."
Well, what did you say?
Um...
I said that I thought
you were a good kisser
and that I liked
your teeny-tiny tushy.
No, not my tushy.
Well, it gets worse.
When asked
if you take initiative
I wrote, "Yes, he was able
to unhook my bra
with minimal supervision..."
And under "Problems
with performance"
I wrote "Dear God, I hope not."
And then, uh... and then I drew
a little smiley face
and then a small
pornographic sketch.
Ross, that is so sweet of you
to get Phoebe that bike.
When I heard
the story
I almost cried.
Almost cried, huh?
Hear that, Chandler?
Almost cried.
Hey, you cry every time
somebody talks about Titanic.
( trembling ):
Those two had only each other.
Phoebe really likes
the bike, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I saw her walking it
down the street the other day.
She had these flowers
in the basket.
It was so cute.
Yeah, I saw her this
morning walking it
by the park.
( quiet laugh )
Wait a minute.
She was walking the bike?
Both times?
Hey, Pheebs.
Oh, hi!
Hi. So, you enjoying
the bike?
Oh, uh-huh.
So much.
Pheebs, you, uh...
you do know how
to ride a bike,
don't you?
Of course.
( uncomfortable laughter )
Can we see
you ride it?
Okay.
( uncomfortable laughter )
See?
See, this is why
I told you
never get involved
with your assistants.
And there is
no such thing
as keeping secrets
when it comes to
having affairs.
Did you hear that, Chandler?
No such thing.
What happened?
I'm just eating candy.
Maybe it's not as bad
as I think, you know?
Maybe they didn't take it
the way I meant it.
Absolutely, you know?
Because "tushy" can mean
both "ass" and "good worker."
Oh, I just got
to get the thing back.
Hey, Rach?
Yeah?
That sketch you
mentioned
might it've
looked a little
something like this?
Oh, my God-- Joey!
What is the matter
with you?
( sighs )
Well, I tell you
this little talent came in handy
before I could afford porn.
( knocking )
Hi, I'm sorry.
I know it's after hours,
but I really need candy.
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
See, rules are rules.
Please, I have people coming
from out of town today
and I told them
all about your candy.
You're kidding?
Out-of-towners, huh?
What'd you tell them?
I told them your candy
was absolutely indescribable.
Well, some people have
been saying it's, you know
little drops of heaven,
but whatever.
Please, can't you help me out?
Hey, Chandler, do
we know that lady?
Maybe.
Isn't she the woman
who lives below you
and has sex really loud?
All right, I'll do
it just this once
but you can't tell anybody.
Yes, yes, please,
just give it to me.
Both:
Yeah, that's her.
It's unbelievable.
I can't believe
that sign didn't work.
You know what would work?
Hmm?
Stop making candy.
But they like it.
You mean they like you.
Maybe.
Is that why you became a chef
so that people would like you?
You really want to talk
about getting people
to like you, huh, funny man?
Okay, now, just remember
everything I taught you
and you'll be
fine, okay?
Here we go.
Ready? Set...
Wait, this seat is
really uncomfortable.
Maybe, before we start,
we should just get another one?
Perhaps like
an airplane seat
or a beanbag chair!
Phoebe, you can't
get out of this, okay?
You have to learn
how to ride a bike.
Why? Why do I have to learn?
Well, in case
of an emergency.
What kind of emergency?
Well, what if a man comes along
and puts a gun to your head
and says "You ride this bike
or I'll sh--
I'll shoot you."
Okay. I would ring the bell
to distract him
and then I would knock the gun
out of his hand
with a Chinese throwing star.
Okay, Phoebe, just, just...
get on the bike and,
hey, I'll hold you up
and push you, okay?
You won't let go?
No.
You swear?
I swear.
Okay.
Come on.
All right, here we go.
Yeah, but hold on.
All right?
All right.
Mm-hmm.
Feel good?
Well...
All right,
try peddling.
Okay. That's it.
You're doing great.
Yes, yes, yes.
Take control.
Yes?
Whee!
Yes! Yes!
Yay!
Oh! Oh! Oh, no!
You swore!
I just thought
you were doing so well...
I am shocked. Shocked!
It's a legitimate
learning technique.
Wow.
( crowd talking )
Hey...
there's some people outside
asking about candy.
Well, they're just
going to have to wait,
aren't they?
I've only got two hands!
Need some help?
No! You don't know the system!
Don't need nobody
messing with the system!
By the way,
the week before your wedding
you may not see a lot of me.
( knocks )
Oh, hello, liar.
Look, I'm, I'm really sorry
I let go of the bike.
I could've been killed,
I hope you know.
I know, I know.
But can we please
try it again, huh?
I mean,
you were so close, Phoebe.
Well, I would love to,
but the bike got stolen
and the police have no suspects.
Phoebe?
What?
( bell ringing )
What the hell?!
All right, you know what?
If you are not going
to learn how to ride this bike
then I'm sorry, I'm just
going to have to take it back.
What? Why?
Because,
because it's...
it'd be like you having
this guitar
and, and never playing it.
Okay, this guitar
wants to be played
and this bike wants
to be ridden and, and
if you don't ride it, you're...
you're killing its spirit.
The bike is dying.
All right.
If you care enough to make up
that load of crap, okay.
Great, great.
You're making the bike
very happy.
( patronizing ):
Okay, Ross.
( whispers ):
Please don't die.
I think we can get
the evaluation back
before they see it
but we'll have to get
into Mr. Zelner's office.
Now, he doesn't get in
until 10:00
so he's no problem,
but his assistant Betty
she comes in early to eat
her breakfast at her desk.
That's kind of sad.
Yeah, well, Betty's kind of sad.
Which is why I believe
I can lure her away
with these chocolates.
Now, while I distract her,
you go in the office.
Got it.
Let's roll.
Hello, Rachel.
You got a minute?
Yeah, sure Mr. Zelner.
For you, anything... a minute.
Okay, great.
Abort the plan.
Abort the plan, abort...
Actually, I'd like
to speak to both of you.
Okay.
Uh, well, can we get
you anything, Mr. Zelner?
Maybe some chocolates?
Um, no, thanks,
but I'll give these to Betty.
So I ready your evaluation
of Tag.
Or to use his full name,
Tag "Sweet Cheeks" Jones.
Something going on with you two?
Oh, my God!
Can you imagine
if there was?
I mean,
what would happen, exactly?
Well, I'd be forced
to file a report.
I'd have to consult
with the legal department
and your future at the company
would be in jeopardy.
Well...
Uh, Mr. Zelner
I'm the one who filled in
that evaluation.
Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
I thought it
would be funny.
You wrote that you have
"a cute tushy"?
Yes.
I have a weird sense of humor
and I'm kind of
strangely proud of my butt.
It's kind of a risky joke, Tag.
And what is this drawing?
I can't figure out what this is.
You're looking at it
upside-down.
You know what?
Doesn't matter.
Hey, it's not like I don't
have a sense of humor, huh?
Hell, I even enjoy a naughty
limerick every now and then.
But there's a time
and a place, huh?
Mmm.
Unless you had a limerick
right now.
No?
Okay.
Well, you've got my fax number.
Mmm.
( both chuckle )
Can't believe you did that.
That was really sweet.
Ah, don't worry about it.
No, you could have
lost your job.
Are you kidding me?
With a cute butt like this,
I'd find work.
Thank you. You're great.
You know what?
What?
I feel great.
In fact...
What?
I... it just... it took me
so long
to get that desk organized.
Oh, I'm sorry.
There it is.
What is going on?
We're waiting
for the candy.
Bring out the candy!
Yeah, lady, give us candy!
( all yelling )
Candy?
What's up, buddy?
What are you doing?
Getting candy.
Get in here.
Hey, and you cannot
smoke in here.
Merry Christmas.
Okay, guys,
the candy is coming.
I just need
another 15 minutes
for the chocolate to cool!
( all clamoring )
All right, everybody, just
be quiet, be quiet, be quiet!
Pipe, pipe, pipe down!
What is the matter
with you people?
This woman was trying
to do a nice thing for you.
She was making candy
so she could try
to get to know all of you
and I'll bet that not one of you
can tell me her name.
Am I right?
Candy Lady?
No, not "Candy Lady."
If we know her,
can we have candy?
All right, you know what?
Forget it.
All of you forget it.
You've ruined it!
Go home! You've ruined it!
( clamoring )
Go on, you guys ruined
everything! You ruined it!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Did you smoke?
No.
Smokes-a-lot Lady
blew smoke
directly into my mouth.
Are you okay?
I'm fine now
but it was really scary
there for a while.
I mean, someone slipped
a threatening note
under the door.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry about that.
Mob mentality
or whatever.
I don't know.
( chuckles )
Wow!
Ooh!
I can't believe it.
I did it.
I rode a bike!
I never thought
I'd be able to do that.
Thank you, Ross.
Oh, hey.
Don't thank me.
Thank yourself.
You're the one
who faced your fears
and ultimately
overcame them.
Don't be so corny, Ross.
It's not
an After School Special.
( laughs )
( bell ringing )